時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
천하를 손에 잡기 위해 다시 성검을 노리는 육도마왕.
Rikudomaoh is looking to get the sacred sword to take the world under his hands.
에도토피아에 나타난 메가톤성은 불을 피워, 지라이얀과 케로키치가 필사적인 소화 활동을 하고 있었다.
Megaton Castle appeared in Edotopia and put on fire, so Jiraiyan and Kerokichi had to put out the fire.
(천수각: 성의 중심에서 제일 높게 만든 망루)
(Tenshukaku: lit. sky guard house; the highest tower within the castle)
그러나 한조는 에도 성의 천수각에서 국왕을 따라잡는다.
But Hanzō caught onto the king at the Tenshukaku of Edo Castle.
그렇지만 센히메의 사랑의 힘으로 불사신 한조를 퇴치하고 국왕을 지켰다.
But the power of Senhime's love managed to get rid of Hanzō and protect the king.
닛코 계획
신겐이오
Nikko Plan
Shingen
타버린 벌판도 아주 잠깐이구나.
The burnt field didn't last long.
에도토피아의 사람들은 억세구나.
The people of Edotopia are robust.
그렇치, 케로키치?
Don't you agree with me, Kerokichi?
무사시는 대체 어쨌어?
Where is Musashi?
늦네요. 출발 시각을 잊었을 리도 없고.
He's late. It's not like he forgot the departure time.
분명 오츠루네 찻집에라도 들러서 단고라도 먹는거 아녀?
Isn't it likely that he's staying at Otsuru's tea store and eating dango?
그래, 있을 법한 일이다.
Yes, that is possible.
아니, 어쩌면, 에도 성 내 부엌에서 먹을 거라도 몰래 탐내고 있는 게...
Or, it's possible that he's looking to sneak foods in the kitchen of Edo Castle.
그런! 무사시가 아무리 식탐이 강하다고 해도 그렇게 한없이 멍청할 거라고는...
No way! Even if Musashi's gluttony is strong, he wouldn't be that endlessly stupid!
아니, 그게, 이전에 송구스럽게도 이에야스 님이 다 드신 진지에서 단무지를 훔쳐 먹어 부엌 관리인에게 크게 혼났습니다.
Well, to tell you the truth, he dared to snitch pickled radish from the leftover of Lord Ieyasu's table,
and he ended up being scolded severely by kitchen administrators.
그거 정말이야?
Are you serious?
미안하오! 다시는 하지 않소!
I'm sorry-dasu! I won't do this again-dasu!
안녕하신가, 센히메, 모두.
Good morning, Senhime and everyone.
어, 안녕, 할아버지!
Good morning, grandpa!
좋은 아침입니다.
Good morning.
아침!
Mornin'!
안녕, 센히메 님. 오늘은 또 정취있는 모습으로. 그 옷은 최근 에도토피아에서 유행하는 것인가요.
Hello, Senhime. You look elegant today as always. Is that cloth popular in Edotopia recently?
에, 아니, 아니, 그런 게!
Er, no, no, not!
좋은 아침입니다, 국왕 전하.
Good morning, your Highness.
슬슬 시각이 되었는데, 준비는 되었나?
It's almost time. Are everyone ready?
그게, 무사시가 아직 안 왔어.
The problem is that Musashi still isn't here.
어라, 아까 보았습니다만.
I saw him before.
그래, 제니가탄하고 일이 있어서 마을에 돌아갔다고 했다.
Yes, he went back to the village since he had something to do with Zenigatan.
이런 할 일 많을 때 마을이라니 어디에!
Where exactly in the village, when we're busy!?
아, 또 오츠루 보러 간 거지?
I guess he went to see Otsuru!
아니, 뭔가 야오젠이라고 하는 곳에 일이 있다고 했다.
No, he said that he had something to do in a place named Yaozen.
야오젠?
Yaozen?
에도토피아 대화 부흥 기념 제 3회 에도토피아 대식 대회 - 야오젠
Edotopia Big Fire Recovery Ceremony - The 3rd Edotopia Eat-A-Lot Contest - Yaozen
지금부터 제 3회 에도토피아 대식 대회를 개최하겠습니다.
The 3rd Edotopia Eat-A-Lot Contest will begin soon.
훌륭한 음식집이오.
What an excellent restaurant-dasu!
야오젠이라고 하면 에도토피아 제일의 가게니까요. 보통은 우리 따위가 얼렁거릴 곳이 아니죠.
Yaozen is the best restaurant in Edotopia. It's not a place that we can casually stop by.
나도 들은 거 있어.
I've heard about this place, too.
비싸오?
Is it expensive-dasu?
비싸니 안 비싸니, 찻밥 하나에 100량이나 한대요.
Expensive or not - it costs 100 ryos for one rice with tea.
어? 100량?
What? 100 ryos!?
아, 시, 실례했습니다.
O- oh, excuse us!
(덴엔초후: 도쿄에서 제일 살기 비싼 곳)
(Denenchōfu: The most expensive area to live in Tokyo)
100량이나 있으면 우리 집 따위는 매일 밥 위에 꽁치하고 계란말이를 위에 올려서 덴엔초후에 집을 세울 수 있지!
With 100 ryos, I can have rice with a saury and rolled eggs on it every day, in a house at Denenchofu!
돈을 던지는 걸 보면 잔뜩 있는 거잖소!
You have a plenty of money, since you throw them around-dasu!
그건 내 직업 도구니까요. 최근은 절약, 절약 해서, 이 던지는 돈조차도 아카네가 왱왱거리고 있어요.
Well, there are the tools for my job! But recently, even Akane is being noisy to me, saying save money, with my tossing coins!
아카네 씨가? 그렇게는 안 보였소...
Ms. Akane does that? She didn't look like she would do that-dasu...
아니, 그것도 이것도 지금의 셋집살이에서 빠져나와서, 독채집을 가지고 싶다고 아카네가 말하니까요. 내가 변변치 못하니.
Akane says that she wants to stop living in a rented house and get a stand-alone house, but I'm so worthless.
큰일이오.
That's problematic-dasu.
아, 옛날이 그립지. 악당 놈들에게 실컷 동전이나 던지던 그 시대가 말야!
Good old days! I miss my days of throwing my tossing coins to bad guys to my heart's content!
지금부터는 돌을 던지면 되오!
You can throw rocks from now on-dasu!
돌이면 가지고 걸어다니기 불편해요! 제니가탄 두목의 트레이드마크를 버리는 것이기도 하고.
Rocks are inconvenient to walk around with! Moreover, that would be throwing away the trademark of Boss Zenigatan.
아, 아카네하고 가정을 꾸렸더니 어지간히 여성 팬이 줄어들었고.
Ever since I made a home with Akane, women fans have been decreased significantly.
그렇게 인기있었소?
You were that popular-dasu?
그야 당연!
Of course!
내가 탐정이 되고 왕왕 유명해지던 때도 큰일이었지요!
When I became a private detective, it was as if there was a uproar to see me!
마을 여자들, 밀어 헤쳐, 밀어 헤쳐, 밀어 헤쳐, 밀어 헤쳐,
Women in the village were pushing their way through infinitely,
어리면 6살 얘부터 늙으면 90살 할매까지 "제니가탄 님! 제니가탄 님!" 하고 참 시끄러워서 말이야!
and from a 6-year-old kiddo to 90-year-old granny were like, "Mr. Zenigatan! Mr. Zenigatan!" and it was so noisy!
돈 때문에라면 가난해지기도 하지
Money makes one poor
좋아하는 고생이라면 낙보다도 즐거워
Hardships that I like are more pleasant than pleasures
성가시군!
How boisterous!
다른 것을 차치하고라도
Even if nothing else
사내라면 기개가 중요해
guts are most important to men
(오캇피키: 탐정; 노래에서는 메캇피키)
(okappiki: private detective; used as mechappiki in the song)
에도토피아의 메카 탐정 협객
The chivalrous mechanical detective of Edotopia
사건이라면 맡겨둬
Leave the incidents to me
알고 있어 데모크라시
I know democracy
내가 정의다 따라와라!
I'm the justice! Follow me!
이야, 샘나오!
You're making me envious-dasu!
그렇죠? 옛날이 좋았지!
You know it! The good old days!
있었네.
You're there.
있었네요.
You are there.
뭘 하고 있냐, 무사시! 나갈 시간은 훨씬 지났어!
What are you doing, Musashi!? It's far past the time to leave!
아니, 잠깐 늦는다고 이에야스 님께 말씀드렸소.
Well, I told Lord Ieyasu that I'll be late for a bit-dasu.
뭐가 잠깐이야? 이렇게 사람 기다리게 하고!
You call this a bit? You made all of us wait!
(할복만으로는 죽지 않으므로 카이샤쿠가 할복하는 자의 목을 침)
(Disembowelment isn't enough for death, so kaishaku beheads whoever that's disemboweling oneself)
할복해라, 무사시!
Disembowel yourself, Musashi!
목은 내가!
I'll behead!
그런! 너무해!
No way! You're cruel!
오늘밤의 봉황환은 잘 벨 것 같구나.
Today night's Hououmaru will do a good job at cutting.
지금 낮이오!
It's daytime now-dasu!
말씀드릴 것이 있습니다.
I have something to say.
뭐냐.
What is it?
에이야스는 국왕과 성검을 남모르게 닛코에 보내려고 하고 있습니다.
Ieyasu is trying to send the king and the sacred sword to Nikko in secret.
뭐라? 닛코에?
What? To Nikko?
닛코는 이에야스의 조상에게 제사를 지내는 신사가 있습니다. 일단 그곳에 숨기려는 것이겠지요.
Nikko is the place where the temple for Ieyasu's ancestors are given prayers. He's trying to hide them there first.
그래. 신겐, 그 조치, 네 궤도주행군단에 맡기겠다. 잘 할 수 있느냐?
I see. Shingen, I will entrust this job to your Track Driving Corps. Can you do it beautifully?
맡겨 주십시오.
Please leave it to me.
지금까지 도쿠간류도 한조도...
Unlike those Dokuganryu and Hanzō....
뭐, 됐다.
Well, that's that.
한조, 도쿠간류 따위와는 달리, 무적이라 불리는 궤도주행군단이 있으니 실패는 생각할 수 없습니다.
Unlike the lowly Hanzō and Dokuganryu, with practically invincible Track Driving Corps, failure is impossible.
잘 말했다!
Well said!
어떻든, 에도 성에서 나오다니, 내 작전은 벌써 성공한 것과 마찬가지.
Anyway, since they're coming out from Edo Castle, my strategy has already succeeded.
다시 나그네 차림으로 짐수레를 끌다니 왠지 이상하오.
Pulling the cart in travel kit again feels weird-dasu.
딱히 준비된 게 없으니까 어쩔 수 없잖아?
It's not like we have things prepared, so it couldn't be helped!
일단 먼저 출발하시겠습니다. 도중 부디 조심해 주십시오.
You'll depart first for now. Please be careful in your way.
예, 저 혼자서 반드시 센히메 님의 목숨을 지켜 보이겠습니다.
Yessir. I will protect Senhime's life only by myself, no matter what.
아, 그러셔?
Oh, yeah?
무사시 씨! 나도 나중에 따라갈게요.
Mr. Musashi! I'll follow you later!
알겠소! 내가 있는 이상 육도마왕 따위 문제가 안 되오!
Roger-dasu! Since I'm here, Rikudomaoh isn't a problem-dasu!
힘내, 무사시!
Do your best, Mr. Musashi!
성검은 주베에게 맡겨 두었습니다. 국왕 전하와 쇼토쿠 님은 저 상자에 들어가 주시길 바랍니다.
I've entrusted the sacred sword to Jūbē. I'd like to ask Your Highness and Shotoku to get inside that box.
저 상자에 국왕 전하를!?
The Highness, in that box!?
닛코에 갈 때까지 참으세요.
Please endure until we reach Nikko.
아니, 그래도...
No, but...
언제 에도 성이 공격당할지 모릅니다. 이 틈에.
We do not know when will Edo Castle be attacked. This is the chance.
자, 쇼토쿠 님도 어서 상자 속에.
Mr. Shotoku, please get into the box immediately.
저도입니까?
Me too?
당연!
Of course!
상자에 들어가서 여행하는 것도 일흥. 자, 들어가자, 쇼토쿠.
A journey inside a box also is a brief entertainment. Let's get in, Shotoku.
예. 그러나 만에 하나 발각되었을 때, 이 인원으로는 부족하기 그지없음이...
Understood. But these people are not enough in cases we got found out.
아니아니, 사람이 너무 많으면 수상해서 들키고 맙니다.
No, no, if we send too many people, it is so suspicious that they'll immediately find out.
걱정이 많구나, 쇼토쿠. 모든 건 센히메 일행에게 맡겨.
You're worried a lot, Shotoku. Leave everything to Senhime and others.
예.
Understood.
자, 출발!
Depart!
힘내겠소.
We'll do our best-dasu!
어차피 변장한다고 해도 소용없는 짓.
Disguising is unnecessary.
여행자로 변장한 무사시 일행은 북으로, 북으로 향해, 닛코 가도에 들어섰다.
Disguised as travellers, Musashi and others headed to north, and entered the Nikko Highway.
기분 나쁠 정도로 아무 일도 없이 무사하게 지나가고 있었다.
They were passing through without any incident, to the extent it's uncanny.
그렇지만.
But...
괜찮아요, 국왕 전하? 힘들지 않으세요?
Are you okay, your Highness? Aren't you tired?
괜찮아. 꽤 쾌적해.
It's alright. It's even pleasant.
만약 뭔가 있으시면 바로 알려 주세요.
If you have something uncomfortable, please tell me right away.
나, 나는 허리가! 이 갑갑함은 좀!
M- my back has problems! It's too narrow here!
아, 그래요.
Oh, I see.
저기.
Hey...
센히메 님. 서두릅시다. 오늘 중으로 도네 강은 넘어갈 생각입니다.
Senhime, let's hurry. We're planning to go over Tone River before the sun sets.
어? 도네 강이라니, 아직 지금부터 200리나 가야 하잖아! 무리야!
(1 ri: 3.9km, 20 ris: 78km; 48.5mi)
What!? We still have to go 20 ris! It's impossible!
무리라도 꾸물대고 있으면 위험합니다. 자.
Impossible or not, it's dangerous to be sluggish over here. Hurry.
힘들어! 지쳤어! 물집이 생겨! 배고파!
I'm tired! I'm exhausted! I'll get blistered! I'm hungry!
그렇지, 무사시?
Don't you agree, Musashi?
괜찮소! 도시락 잔뜩 가져왔으니까!
I'm okay-dasu! I took a lot of lunch boxes-dasu!
아, 그래.
Oh, I see.
전진 중단!
Stop advancing!
전원 공격 태세!
Everyone, into offensive setup!
거리 200!
Distance 200!
국왕의 목숨이 위험하다! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
The life of the king is at stake! Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
쏴라!
Open fire!
배를 보내오!
Now sailing off-dasu!
대포인가!
Cannons!
이대로는 안 되겠어.
This isn't good.
나리!
Sir!
가져왔수!
I took this!
좋다!
Great!
뭐가 문제냐, 반격도 못 하냐?
What's the problem? Can't you even counterattack?
그런 곳에 숨어서 우리 궤도주행군단에게서 도망칠 수 있다 생각했냐? 멍청한 놈들이!
Did you think that you could escape my Track Driving Corps by hiding at a place like that? You fools!
궤도주행군단?
Track Driving Corps?
뭣이오, 그게!?
What's that-dasu!?
모르냐! 나느 육도마왕의 부하 하면 누구나 아는 신겐이다!
Don't you know Shingen, whom everyone gets reminded of, when one says Rikudomaoh's subordinate!?
신겐?
Shingen?
어? 신겐? 중원이라면 알고 있소.
What? Shingen? I know smidgen-dasu!
네놈 무사시렷다!
You brat must be Musashi!
그렇소! 내가 유명한 이천일류, 미야모토 마을의 무사시이오!
That's right-dasu! I'm that famous Musashi from Miyamoto village of Nitenichiryu-dasu!
네이놈! 잠깐 놀아주려 했더니 기고만장해가지고는! 국왕과 성검을 넘기면 넘어가지만 그리하지 않으면 모두 불바다에 빠트린다!
You brat! I see that you're too elated for me to play with!
I'll let this pass if you hand over the king and the sacred sword, but if you don't, you're all gonna sink into the sea of fire!
불바다에 빠지는 건 네놈이다!
You're the one to sink into the sea of fire!
이 신겐에게 얘들 장난같은 요술은 안 통한다! 쏴라!
A child's magic doesn't work against me, Shingen! Open fire!
어떻게든 될 것 같습니까, 제니가탄 님.
Do you think you can do something with this, Mr. Zenigatan?
맡겨 주쇼.
Leave it to me.
어라? 이상하네.
Huh? That's weird.
어이! 왜 그래! 어이!
Hey! What's wrong? Hey!
별 거 아니네.
That was easy.
자, 나리, 어서!
Now, sir, hurry!
좋습니다.
Right.
그래도 이건 대단한 장치네요!
Anyway, this is one interesting machinery!
움직일 수 있겠습니까.
Do you think you can operate?
맡겨 주쇼. 장치에 대해선 쫌 자신이 있으니.
Leave it to me. I'm pretty confident when it comes to machinery.
그래, 이거구나!
So, this must be it!
갑니다!
We're going!
부탁드립니다.
Please do so.
대열에서 벗어나지 마라, 멍청아!
Do not get out from the line, you fool!
뭐야!?
What!?
오 마이 갓!
oh my god!
뭔 일이야, 대체?
What's going on?
잘 모르겠소. 이 틈에 달아나오!
I don't know-dasu. Let's run using this chance-dasu!
네이놈! 배신자를 쫒아라! 쫒아!
You bastard! Get that traitors! Get them!
제기랄!
Damn!
산에 도망치다니 실패구나. 뭐, 어차피 달아날 곳 없는 쥐와 다를 게 없지.
It's a failure for now, since they hid into the mountain. But still, they're nothing more than rats without a place to hide.
내일 아침 총공격해 주겠다. 목숨이 거기까지인줄 알아라!
We'll do an all-out attack tomorrow morning. Assume that your life ends then!
이건 뭐라 하나?
How do you call this?
구운 단고라 합니다.
Those are roasted dangos.
꽤 맛있는 것이구나.
They're pretty delicious.
입에 맞으니 다행이요.
Great to know that you like these.
오츠루의 구운 단고는 지팡구 제일이오.
Otsuru's roasted dangos are the best of jipang-dasu.
이야, 꽤나 맛있어.
These are pretty delicious!
어라? 그러고 보니 코지로는 어디 갔소?
Huh? Where's Kojirō, by the way-dasu?
지금 망을 보고 있어요.
He's working as a guard.
그럼 내가 단고 가져다 주고 올게.
Then I'll go give him dangos.
센히메 님은 정말 마음이 착하시네요.
Senhime, you're really kind.
아, 그런!
Oh, my!
어라, 저런. 먼지 불어내면 괜찮아.
Oh, my. They'll be fine if I blow off dusts!
죽지는 않아.
He won't die.
고독한 강한 사내는
To a lonely strong man,
이기는 일마저도
even winning
쓰라려지지
is painful
고독한 고운 사내는
A lonely tender man
사랑하는 사람에게는
becomes cold
차가워지지
to lovers
어둠에 흔들리는 도시 불빛
Shaking in darkness, City Light
뜻대로 안 되는 세상 풍조
The tide of the world isn't following my will
파란 하늘의 제비처럼
Like a swallow in the blue sky
바람을 갈라
Cutting through the wind
요동치는 하늘길을 날아가는 제비
I'm a swallow flying through the disordered sky
파란 하늘의 제비
Swallow in the blue sky
혼자서
On all one's own
언젠가 또다른 외로운 새가
Until the day that another lonely bird
앞질러가는 그 날까지
gets ahead of me
아, 센히메 님. 듣고 계셨습니까. 부끄...
Ah, Senhime, you were listening to my song? How embarassing...
잘 하잖아, 코지로?
Aren't you good, Kojirō?
종종 상자노래방에 가니까요...
I often use karaoke boxes...
여기, 단고 먹어!
Here! Have some dangos!
네! 잘 먹겠습니다!
Yes! Thank you!
단고에 돌이...
There're stones in dangos...
그래? 왜일까, 이상하네!
Really? How could that be? That's weird!
그런데, 주베 님.
By the way, Mr. Jūbē...
지금부터 어떻게 빠져나갈 생각입니까.
How we are going to slip out from now on?
전차 하나로는 이길 턱이 없으니 말이죠.
We can't possibly win with only one tank.
그렇소! 다들 전차에 태우고 달아나오!
That's it-dasu! We'll get everyone onto the tank and run-dasu!
그래도 그 전차에 모두 탈 수 있는 건 아니야.
But it's not like everyone can get onto that tank.
아니오! 내 생각을 들어 보시오!
No-dasu! Listen to my idea-dasu!
신겐 님! 저걸!
Lord Shingen! Look at that!
전원 출격 태세!
Everyone, sortie formation!
멍청한 놈들. 노려 쏠 뿐이다!
Those fools. We'll just snipe them!
쏴라!
Open fire!
신겐 님. 숨통을 끊어 놓는 것도 시간의 문제군요.
Lord Shingen. Bringing them down is only a matter of time.
그래. 그래도 이렇게 멍청하게 도망가다니...
Yes, but I didn't think that they would choose such a foolish way of running...
어?
Huh?
보아하니 작전은 성공한 듯 하오.
It seems that our plan has worked-dasu.
해냈구나!
You did it!
역시 속임수였군.
I knew it was a trickery.
신겐! 적이지만 잘 알아냈다!
Shingen! I must praise you for finding that out, even though you're our enemy!
정말이오!
True-dasu!
국왕! 목숨은 잘 가져가겠다!
King! I'll take your life!
잠깐 기다리시오, 신겐! 1:1의 승부를 바라오!
Wait a moment-dasu! Shingen, I want an one-to-one fight-dasu!
뭣이!?
What!?
만약 내가 이기면 우리를 보내주시오!
If I win, let us just go-dasu!
지면?
What if you lose?
지지는 않소.
We do not lose.
칼 들어라, 무사시!
Grab your sword, Musashi!
바라던 바이오!
I was just about to do that-dasu!
꽤 하는구나, 무사시.
You're pretty good, Musashi.
신겐이야말로이오.
Shingen, you too-dasu.
잡았소!
I got you-dasu!
비겁하오! 1:1 승부이오!
That's cowardly! It's an one-to-one fight!
그런 거 난 약속 안 했다!
I never promised you that!
그럼 우리가 상대해 주어도 괜찮겠지?
Then you must be fine with we facing you!
신겐, 달려들어라!
Shingen, face us!
비겁해!
How cowardly!
오늘은 이쯤에서 해 두겠다!
This is it for today!
메롱!
Pfft!
무사시 일행의 대활약으로 국왕 일행은 무사하게 닛코에 겨우 도착했다.
Thanks to the great activities of Musashi and others, the king managed to reach Nikko safely.
그렇지만 무사시는 다음에 신겐과 대면하는 때, 그 때야말로 이 강적과 우열을 가려야 할 것이라고 각오를 했다.
But Musashi made a resolution to himself
that he'll have to settle the superiority with this strong enemy when they meet next time.
강한 사내는 강한 사내를 알아보는 법이었다.
A strong man can recognize another strong man.
싸우고 맞았어
I fought and I got beaten
코피 쓩이야 랑데부
Nosebleed drips rendezvous
나도 지지 않으려 한발!
I can't lose, so take my blow!
핀치 펀치로 대역전
Pinch! Punch! I won by reversal
다음 시간 즐거운
Next is delightful lunchtime
급식일 텐데
But it's not delightful today
선생님의 벼락이
The thunder of my teacher
나한테만 떨어져 왔어
only hit me and nobody else
사정을 말해도
I tried to explain
들어주지 않는 채
But he won't listen
어떻게 해도 역시
Now whatever I do
눈물이 나오고 말아
I end up crying
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
왠지 안타까워
you'll feel downhearted
메가톤성을 쫒아 우리는 세토 내해로 향했소.
Chasing Megaton Castle, we headed to Seto Inland Sea-dasu.
그런데 오츠루가 뒤를 쫒아와서 센짱하고 여자의 다툼.
But Otsuru followed us and is doing women's quarrel with Sen-chan.
그 때, 센짱이 한조의 함정에 빠져 잡히고 말았소.
At that time, Sen-chan fell into Hanzō's trap and was caught-dasu.
젠장! 이건 어떻게든 해야 하오!
Damn! I have to do something about this-dasu!
다음 이야기! 목마는 무서운 함정이었소
Next story! The Wooden Horse was a Trap
질풍노도의 오츠루이오!
It's the stormy Otsuru-dasu!
다음 이야기
목마는 무서운
함정이었소
기대하세요!
Next Episode
The Wooden Horse
was a Trap
Look forwards for it!